Try me!

#### Contact

phone +31622040319
email info@arejo.nl
location The Hague,
Netherlands
github github
portfolio portfolio
linkedin LinkedIn

#### About me

# Startup founder turned developer.

Extremely passionate about building beautiful, practical and smart things. Selfstarting, highly determined, obsessively persistent.

Having completed the Frontend section of the Full-Stack Career Course on codecademy, I am eager to practice my new found skills as a Front-end / React Developer.

Open for a junior position or Freelance assignment. Remote / hybrid preferred. Get in touch!

## Experience

2021 - Current Arejas The Hague

2019/2022 Arejas The Hague

2010-2019 privately held

2016-2017 Camptoo.nl The Hague

2015-2016 Yippie.nl Amsterdam

2011-2014 OWNR The Hague

#### Becoming a Full-Stack JavaScript Developer

Bootcamp on Codecademy, Studying React / Express. Build and sold a campervan to be able to study fulltime. See: Education / About me.

#### Freelance Developer

Wordpress websites & webshops for different clients using Divi, Elementor, WooCommerce, HTML and CSS.

#### mijnJohan.nl

Development, Marketing and Sales. Homegrown accountancy software for independent entrepreneurs. Passive Income Company.

#### Growth Hacker

Head responsible for the growth of the product-offering for this peer-2-peer Campers & Caravans renting platform, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

## First marketing Officer

Head responsible for the first growth spurt in users of this shopping-app, using the complete online marketing spectrum including Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Goal Tracking, Analytics, Split Testing and Conversion Optimisation.

#### Startup Founder

Internet startup in action sports. Responsible for marketing, sales, investors, product-development and allround succes. Collaborations with among others: Quiksilver / DC shoes and Nitro Snowboards.

## **Key Skills**

Building web-apps from start to finish Rocking React & Redux

## Tech Skills

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
React
Redux
Node.js
Express.js
SQL
Git
GitHub
TDD
Mocha
JEST
React Testing Library
JSON

## **Education**

2021 - Present

2020 - 2021 codecademy

2008-2010 WdKa Rotterdam

1998-2004 Ashram College Alphen aan den Rijn

## Full-Stack Developer Career Path Course

Becoming a Full-Stack web developer learning to build web-apps' front-end and back-end using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node, Express, SQL, TDD, Mocha, Jest, React Testing Library, Markdown, JSON, Git & Github.

## Build a back-end app with JavaScript

A predecessor to codecademy's back-end engineer career path. This was my introduction to JavaScript, Node, Express, SQL and building API's.

## **Creative Advertising**

Art Direction, concepting  $\&\ realisation.$  Arts Academy of Rotterdam.

## Atheneum

Atheneum. Focus on Economics & Society. Field of choice: Computer Science. Research paper: Encryption.

## **Marketing Skills**

Google Analytics
Goal Tracking
Growth Hacking Principles
Split Testing
Conversion Optimalisation
Google Adwords
Facebook Ads

## Additional Skills

Adobe Creative Suite Google Sketchup SCRUM Agile

## Certifications

• Back-end app with Javascript | Write API's with Node, Express & SQL | Codecademy | Jan '21

## Languages

Dutch English German Spanish

## Hobbie

Snowboarding Skateboarding Surfing Wakeboarding Climbing Guitar Travel Campervans